[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a pangolin?", "correct_answer": "A scaly ant-eating mammal", "incorrect_answers": ["A poisonous snake", "A type of fish", "A type of waterfowl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal was the color taupe named after?", "correct_answer": "Mole", "incorrect_answers": ["Horse", "Bear", "Sparrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a grape variety used for producing Champagne?", "correct_answer": "Cabernet Franc", "incorrect_answers": ["Pinot Meunier", "White Chardonnay", "Red Pinot Noir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pound for pound, humans are not the strongest animals. What is considered the strongest species, pound for pound?", "correct_answer": "The Hercules beetle", "incorrect_answers": ["The leaf-cutting ant", "The red ant", "The atlas roach"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snake skin is covered in scales.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spectroscopic analysis revealed that Plutos surface is composed mainly of this element.", "correct_answer": "Nitrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxygen", "Carbon", "Ozone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the supposed beneficial property of the Blood Orchid that is the object of the search in the 2004 horror thriller movie Anacondas: The Hunt for the Blood Orchid?", "correct_answer": "It prolongs life.", "incorrect_answers": ["It makes its owner extremely lucky.", "It gives eternal happiness.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following people was not awarded the Nobel Peace Prize?", "correct_answer": "John Paul II", "incorrect_answers": ["Marthin Luther King Jr.", "Nelson Mandela", "Yasser Arafat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who delivered these words: \u201dSo you\u2019d better grow eyes in the back of your head cause you won\u2019t see it coming?", "correct_answer": "Matt Dillon in My Bodyguard", "incorrect_answers": ["John Travolta in Pulp Fiction", "Christopher Lee in The Man With the Golden Gun", "Keifer Sutherland in Stand By Me"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Wizard of Oz, Dorothy lives with her aunt Em and her uncle whose name is what?", "correct_answer": "Uncle Henry", "incorrect_answers": ["Uncle Harry", "Uncle Charlie", "Uncle Tom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fibromyalgia can be diagnosed with a simple blood test.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In May 2009 the Tasmanian devil was declared to be endangered because this disease had almost wiped out its population.", "correct_answer": "Facial cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["AIDS", "Kawasaki disease", "Rabies"]}]